<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <language id="belarus">
    <entry id="str_dlc_available"><![CDATA[DLC Available]]></entry>
    <entry id="menu_base_element_restore_purchase"><![CDATA[Restore DLC Purchases]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_needs_dlc"><![CDATA[You need to purchase the following DLC to load this save:]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_title"><![CDATA[Buy DLC]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_connecting_itunes_store"><![CDATA[Connecting to iTunes Store...]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_title_crimson_court"><![CDATA[Darkest Dungeon®: The Crimson Court]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_description_crimson_court"><![CDATA[Darkest Dungeon®: The Crimson Court is the first expansion for the award-winning grim and gothic RPG by Red Hook Studios. Crimson Court is a parallel campaign experienced alongside the main Darkest Dungeon content that will provide you with new challenges and variation at every difficulty level. The narrative grounding sheds some light on the Ancestor’s early days, and will be presented in the same style of cut-scenes you’ve seen elsewhere in the game.

Features:
* A new hero class: The Flagellant!
* A new dungeon region: The Courtyard
* A full faction of new deadly foes
* 5 new Bosses with some of the most complex and devious mechanics yet.
* A new wandering boss: The Fanatic
* Districts: 10 new buildings to upgrade your Town
* Massive, sprawling maps with locked doors, prisoner rooms, and progress saves
* Lore-driven trinket sets for all heroes - with set bonuses!

As the Crimson Curse spreads unrelentingly over the estate, parties will battle new enemies in familiar regions, as well as setting foot in a completely new sprawling environment: the Courtyard. There, amidst unique curios, traps and obstacles, a complete faction of new blood-crazed foes lie in wait, overseen by three distinct boss encounters. These slavering enemies and epic encounters will introduce new combat mechanics, testing the limits of your favorite strategies.

As the infestation grows and your roster begins to sicken, the Fanatic will emerge to roam the hallways, confusing friend and foe alike in his zealous quest to exterminate the Curse.

The odds are not completely stacked against you, however! A new playable hero class will be added alongside powerful new trinkets, town events, and a fresh way to expand and upgrade your Hamlet.]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_short_details_crimson_court"><![CDATA[Darkest Dungeon®: The Crimson Court is the first expansion for the award-winning grim and gothic RPG by Red Hook Studios. The Crimson Court enhances any Darkest Dungeon campaign with the addition of a new storyline and dungeon, new hero class, new monsters, new bosses, the Fanatic wandering miniboss, set trinkets for every hero, and new buildings...]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_title_shieldbreaker"><![CDATA[Darkest Dungeon®: The Shieldbreaker]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_description_shieldbreaker"><![CDATA[The Shieldbreaker is a powerful ally in the fight to reclaim the Estate and banish the evil that squats in the Darkest Dungeon. A highly-tactical and solid damage dealing hero, she truly excels when countering monsters with high protection and those who guard their allies. Her movement, speed, and targeted abilities make her a valuable ally for dismantling intractable monster groups. Though relatively low health, the Shieldbreaker is yet highly survivable in short bursts thanks to her Aegis scales.

Features:
* New hero class: the Shieldbreaker
* Shieldbreaker class-specific trinkets, including a lore set
* 3 New Monsters - frightful illusions from the Shieldbreaker's origin, now slithering forward to infest the Estate
* New Consumable Item - Aegis Scale, providing a last bastion of protection for when a hero truly needs it.]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_short_details_shieldbreaker"><![CDATA[The Shieldbreaker DLC adds an all new recruitable hero into Darkest Dungeon. She is a powerful tactical combatant, able to pierce armor, break guards, and poison foes. The DLC also includes several new monsters and a new consumable item type: the Aegis Scale!]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_title_color_of_madness"><![CDATA[Darkest Dungeon®: The Color of Madness]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_description_color_of_madness"><![CDATA[Some hateful shard of alien origin has streaked through the night sky, crashing into the old Miller’s farm on the outskirts of the Hamlet!  Those unfortunate enough to witness the Comet’s arrival have been blinded by what they can only describe as a shifting, ephemeral hue of damnably abrasive intensity.  There has been no word from the farm in a fortnight, save for the unearthly groaning that echoes from the ruin of the mill…

“When men shake hands with time, time crushes them like tumblers; little pieces of glass.”
― Abu al-Ala al-Ma'arri

Features
* New region: The Farmstead!
* Endless Quest: Survive as long as you can while getting lost in time and space, confronted by unending waves of enemies new and old, pushing ever closer to the crash site of the Comet.
* Twisted new trinkets, available for purchase from the Jeweler. Put your gold away—he trades only in Comet Shards!
* All-New Enemy Faction: The Miller and his loyal workmen have become eerie husks of their former selves.
* 3 new bosses - The Miller, The Thing From the Stars, and the Comet itself!
* New Curios help keep your party in fighting shape as you face the enless hordes!
* Expand your Hamlet with 4 new District buildings and reap their benefits.
* New Quirks, with unique and powerful effects!
* Our biggest soundtrack addition yet from Stuart Chatwood]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_short_details_color_of_madness"><![CDATA[Some hateful shard of alien origin has streaked through the night sky, crashing into the old Miller’s farm on the outskirts of the Hamlet!  Those unfortunate enough to witness the Comet’s arrival have been blinded by what they can only describe as a shifting, ephemeral hue of damnably abrasive intensity.  There has been no word from the farm in a fortnight, save for the unearthly groaning that echoes from the ruin of the mill…]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_title_musketeer"><![CDATA[Darkest Dungeon®: The Musketeer]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_description_musketeer"><![CDATA["I ain't afraid to love a man. I ain't afraid to shoot him either." -Annie Oakley

A celebrated competitive sharpshooter, The Musketeer arrives in the Hamlet, determined to prove her skill after a disappointing tournament. She aims to become a legend in hunting circles by putting her skills to the test against the terrifying beasts and unnameable abominations that roam the Ancestor's Estate!

* New hero class: The Musketeer (mechanically identical to Arbalest)
* Musketeer class-specific trinkets.

Once exclusive to a select group of our Kickstarter backers, the Musketeer is now FREE DLC for all Darkest Dungeon® owners! She is a complete, studio quality, re-skin of the Arbalest class.  The Musketeer has access to her own set of class trinkets and will be available in the Stagecoach like the other Darkest Dungeon® heroes!]]></entry>
    <entry id="str_buydlc_short_details_musketeer"><![CDATA[The Musketeer is a FREE DLC hero class which was only available to upper-tier Kickstarter backers. She is complete, high quality re-skin of the Arbalest class.]]></entry>
  </language>
</root>

